BILEN GERAWORK

Media Designer

PROFILE

I am media engineering graduate from Metropolia UAS specialized in Audiovisual Technology and Human-Computer-Interaction. I am highly motivated and into culture, literature, arts and history. I believe in ethical storytelling. Products will be successful when they help tell a story.



KIRJANPITÄJÄNKUJA 5 A 5



geraworkbilen@gmail.com



+358451295959



EDUCATION

MA Aalto University ARTS, New media design and production, 2017-present

BSC (Media Engineering) Helsinki Metropolia UAS 2012-2016

Electrical and computer engineering AAiT, 2009-2012

SKILLS

FIGMA

ADOBE TOOLS ILLUSTRATOR, IN-DESIGN

POWERPOINT

GRAPHICS

PRODUCTIVITY

VISUAL PROGRAMMING

EXPERTISE

PROJECT DESIGN

WEB DESIGN

MOBILE INTERFACES

PRODUCTIVITY TOOLS

REPORT WRITING

SOCIAL MEDIA

EXPERIENCE

QUALITY ENGINEER- LABELING

- Design and develop labeling for medical devices using different softwares and databases.
- Create labels and IFUs for vyaire products.
- Innovations on workflow and quality of products.

GRAPHIC ARTIST

- Graphics and video content making and social campaigns as well as branding
- Develop communication with clients and or directors to know what the work requires in advertising.
- · Work on different advertising campaigns

WEB DEVELOPER

- 5 months internship at Bookndo –Front-end development & UI design using Bootstrap framework (HTML, CSS and javascript)
- Create a mental picture of what each solutions should look like from the user perspective and gather resources to this effect. Design and implement solutions with in a team.

VYAIRE MEDICAL HELSINKI

MAR 2021-PRESENT

BERRY ADVERTISING ADDIS ABABA

2014-2017

BOOKNDO OY HELSINKI MAY-SEPT